Hello.
こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張してます?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It's not scary at all.
全然怖くないですよ
Thank you for your support.
よろしくお願いしますね
What should I call you today?
今日なんて呼びしたらいいですか?
If it's something other than your real name.
本名以外だったら
Anything.
何でも
Have you ever been told that you are going to a tournament?
なんか大会に行っているとかって言われない?
Like Horimi Mana-chan.
堀美雅奈ちゃんとか
Horimi Mana-chan?
堀美雅奈ちゃん?
surely.
確かに
Then, should I choose Miyana-chan?
じゃあ美雅奈ちゃんでいいですか?
Ah, that's it please.
あ、それでお願いします
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
yes.
はい
How old are you?
お いくつですか?
I'm 20 years old now.
今20歳です
20 years old?
20歳?
Now you can drink alcohol.
お酒飲めるようになったね
that's right.
そうです
Do you like alcohol?
お酒好きですか?
Not much.
あんまり
It's about normal.
普通ぐらいです
What do you drink?
何飲むの?
There are many sweet ones.
甘いやつが多いです
Not much?
あんまり?
Is beer okay?
ビールとかダメ?
still.
まだ
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I'm a strong drinker.
お酒強いよ
I guess it's about normal.
普通ぐらいかな
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
Have you ever made a mistake with alcohol?
お酒でやらかしたことはまだない?
Not yet.
まだないです
good.
よかった
Do you know what we're going to do today?
今日何するかって知ってます?
What are you doing today?
今日何しますか?
Today is...
今日は...
If you don't communicate properly, you'll get arrested for having sex with an uncle.
ちゃんと伝わってないと、 おじさん不動意性交渉で捕まっちゃう
So.
ので
What are you doing today?
今日 何します?
今日何してるの?
Yes, we meet.
そう、会ってます
I'll take a picture of it and upload it on the internet.
それを撮って、 インターネットでアップしちゃいますけど、
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
It's so cute.
すごい可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
you're welcome.
どういたしまして
cute.
可愛い
Thank you for coming.
来てくれてありがとうございます
you're welcome.
こちらこそ
So, can I have you stand up?
じゃあ、立ってもらっていいですか?
Is your fashion always like this?
いつもこういうファッションなの?
Well, I guess there are quite a lot of skirts.
そうですね、スカートが割と多いかも
Do you like skirts?
ス カート好きなの?
yes.
はい
It's Uncle Skirt's favorite.
スカートおじさんの大好物なんです
Do you feel sick?
気持ち悪いですか?
good.
いい
He's such a good kid.
すごい良い子ですね
Was it Manami-chan?
マナミちゃんでしたっけ?
What was that?
何でしたっけ?
My name is Miona.
ミオナです
Miona-chan is a good girl.
ミオナちゃん良い子ですね
What is your hobby?
趣味って何ですか?
Hobby...I wonder what it is.
趣味...何だろう
I like watching movies.
映画とか見るの好きです
Surprisingly, it's indoors.
意外とインドアなので
Everyone watches a lot of movies.
みんな結構映画見てるね
I probably spend more time at home than taking shots like this.
こんなショットで出るよりも家にいることの方が多いかもです
Should I watch it at home instead of at the movie theater?
映画館で見るんじゃなくて家で見るの?
It's home.
家です
Well, it's a bit hot, so let's go to bed.
じゃあちょっと暑いんで寝ちゃいましょうか
If you like, can I leave it on the futon?
良かったら布団の上で置いとく?
yes.
はい
What's wrong with getting it dirty?
汚しちゃうとあれなんで
I feel like I can walk with it.
なんかそれでもで歩けそうね
If you put it down.
下かけば
Miona was wearing underwear like this.
ミオナちゃんこんなに下着履いてたんだって
Please take a look.
見て ください
Aren't you popular?
モテませんか?
What do you think?
どうだろう
Is that how much of a person you are?
そういうくらい人なの?
I don't know.
わかんない
You'll be popular, right?
モテるでしょ
It's cute.
可愛いもんね
Do you want to turn your back?
後ろ向けますか?
Facing the front.
正面向いて
So, can I have you take off my bra?
じゃあブラジャー取ってもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
She had breasts like that.
そんなおっぱいしてたんですね
How many cups are there?
何カップあるんですか?
It's a C cup.
Cカップです
Are you satisfied?
満足してます?
満足してる?
Even though it's big, it's heavy.
大きくても重くてね
It's a big mess.
大きくめちゃもんね
So, can I lick Miona's breasts now?
じゃあもうミオナちゃんのおっぱい舐めちゃっていいですか?
May I?
いいですか?
Then please sit there.
じゃあそこ座ってください
What is your favorite food?
好きな食べ物は何ですか?
My favorite food is sweets.
好きな食べ物は甘いものが好きです
Do you like sweets?
甘いものが好き?
yes.
はい
I've maintained my figure pretty well.
結構体型は維持してるね
Please be careful.
気をつけてね
But just a little.
でもちょっとだけ
It's not like I'm paying too much attention to books.
本でガチガチに気をつけてるとかでもないけど
Seriously?
マジ?
It's late.
遅いね
There are hundreds of men waiting on the other side of the camera.
カメラの向こうに何百人って男が肩から待機してるんで
My hands are fat.
手が太ってますから
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
That's really slow.
すごい遅いね
It touches my skin.
肌すれすれ
As expected of a 20 year old.
さすが20歳
It smells really good though.
めちゃくちゃいい匂いするんですけど
It's really delicious.
すごい美味しいです
Move your butt a little more forward.
もうちょっとお尻前面にして
It smells like blueberries.
ブルーベリーの香りがします
Really.
本当に
Definitely not.
絶対しない
This is a blueberry scent
これブルーベリーの香り
but.
が
Touch it like this on the sofa.
ソ ファーの上でこういう風に触れます
So next time I'll touch on it like this.
じゃあ次、こうやって触れます
Can I touch your butt?
お尻触っていいですか?
amazing.
すごい
Can I touch your butt hole for a moment?
ちょっとお尻の穴当てていいですか?
here?
ここ?
No, here?
違う、ここ?
Yeah.
うん
here?
ここ?
Don't you want your ass here?
ここお尻いらないの?
Can I take a moment to discuss this?
ちょっとお間をこれに当てていいですか?
here?
ここ?
Can I take down your pants?
パンツをおろしていいですか?
Yeah.
うん
yes.
はい
Just beat Saraka.
ちょっと 手さらか倒して
Oh yeah, nice, nice.
そうそう、いいねいいね
Now, let's take down your pants, shall we?
じゃあパンツをおろしちゃいましょうか、
Completely.
完全にね
Can I get some pants?
パンツもらっていいですか?
a,
あ、
Put on the sheet.
シ ートつけて
That's beautiful.
あれ、綺麗ですね
Then please turn this way.
じゃあこっち向いてください
Everyone please stand here.
こっち全員立ってください
This is how I have it.
こうやって持ってます
Please bring your pants to the side.
パンツとかを横に持ってきてください
Can I ask you to tell me that these are my pants?
これ私のパンツですって言ってもらっていいですか?
These are my pants.
これ私のパンツです
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Then please tighten it.
じゃあそれ締まってください
I'll take another thumbnail then.
じゃあまたサムネ撮りますね
Ah, but it's okay.
あ、でもいいよいいよ
That look is nice.
その姿はいいね
Please turn this way.
こっち向いてください
It's the cashier.
キャッシャーですね
Are you taking pictures?
撮ってるの?
yes.
はい
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Okay, I don't like it.
オッケー、嫌だな
Are you spreading your legs a little?
ちょっと足広げてますか?
Ah, I'm curious.
あ、気になる
be on one's mind.
気になる
What is your charm point?
自分のチャームポイントはどこですか?
Charm point...
チャームポイント...
Tear bag...
涙袋...
Tearbags... so cute.
涙袋...かわいい
surely.
確かに
So, can you change your image?
じゃあイメージ改革できますか?
On that sofa.
そのソファーで
Looks like a great model.
すごいモデルさんみたいね
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいですね
Would you like to spread your pussy a little?
ちょっとおまんこ広げますか?
Well then, thank you for your help today.
じゃあ今日はよろしくお願いしますね
Did you wash it properly?
綺麗に洗った?
Can you put your hands behind your head?
両手を頭の後ろに持ってこえる?
The sides...
脇が...
I can't see it in the middle.
真ん中に見えない
Please open it and take it down.
開いて下ろしてください
It smells really good.
めっちゃいい匂いする
washed
洗った
So, it's outstanding.
から、 抜群ですね
Well then, let's move to the bed.
じゃあベッドの方移動しましょうかね
Would you like to lie down with your head over here?
こっち頭で横になりますか?
It smells amazing.
すごい匂いする
すごい 匂 いする
Can I lick your bottom?
下舐めていいですか?
yes.
はい
Do it.
しなさい
Let's wait.
待ちましょう
Can I spread it out?
広げていい?
I'll spread it out.
広げますよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
The girl's membranes are more cracked.
少女膜下の方が割れてるんだね
Did it hurt the first time?
最初の時痛かった?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It's quite cracked.
結構割れてる
It hurts because the first person pierces the membrane, but
最初の人が 膜を突きあぶるから痛いんだけど、
Even after it is torn, it remains engraved in your body for the rest of your life.
裂けた後って、一生体に刻み込まり続ける
The bottom is torn.
下の方が裂けてる
What do you think?
どう思います?
I'll clean it up a bit.
ちょっとクリーン剥きますよ
It's clean and small.
クリーン小さいね
born
生
Is that so?
き そうなの?
How many centimeters tall are you?
身長何センチあるんですか?
It is 155 cm.
155センチです
155 cm.
155センチ
It's very thin.
すごい細いですね
When did your breasts start getting bigger?
おっぱいはいつくらいから大きくなり始めたんですか?
when?
いつ?
Junior high school student?
中学生?
About junior high school students.
中学生くらい
So, a little bit.
で、ちわちわと
yes.
そう
Are there any idols or actresses that you aspire to?
目指してるアイドルとか女優さんっているんですか?
I feel like I want to be like this person.
なんかこういう人の感じになりたいみたいな
I like K-Pop idols.
K-POPのアイドルとか好きです
It's K-POP.
K-POPなんだ
I'm so happy.
すごい幸せです
That's cool.
かっこいいな
happiness.
幸せ
It's so cute that it's hairless.
毛つないくらい可愛いね
It's cute.
可愛いね
What kind of tricks did you have in your previous life?
前世でどんなとこつんだろう?
You can be that cute.
そんな可愛くなれる
Can you put your face on the bed and spread your ass hole with both hands?
顔をベッドにつけて両手でお尻が穴広げれる?
Do you want me to cum inside you?
中に出してほしい?
Yeah.
うん
Please ask me to cum inside you.
私は中に出してくださいってお願いしてください
Please take it inside.
中に出してください
Please give me as much as possible.
いっぱい出してくださいってお願いしてください
Please give me as much as you can.
い っぱい出してください
Can you hold it with both hands?
両足手で持てる?
Do you forcefully insert blood cells into your butthole?
お尻の穴に血球で力入れて入れる?
And I'll put it in with the one inside.
そして 中のやつで入れるから
Can you spread it with both hands?
両手で広げられる?
Everyone showed a lot of their true intentions.
みなさん本意をちょっといっぱい出しちゃった
Let's just put that in there.
ちょっとそれ入れてみよっか
You can put it in and take it out a little.
少し出し入れできる
I have to make the most of it.
出し切りなきゃ
Then itself.
そしたらそれ自身
Let's take it in and take it out a little.
ちょっと出し入れしてみよっか
So let's put that in.
じゃあそれ入れてみよっか
It's a little thick so it's as far as I can go.
ちょっと太いからいけるところまで
That's great.
すごいいけるね
amazing.
すごい
It's a leg hole.
足の穴ですよ
Please take it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れしてね
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Please go home without washing.
洗わずに帰ってね
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
I can put it in and take it out a little bit.
ちょっと出し入れできる
I have to make the most of it.
出し切りなきゃ
A bit on its own.
ちょっとそれ自身
Let's put it in and take it out a little bit.
ちょっと出し入れしてみよっ
mosquito.
か
Well then, let's put that in.
じゃあ それ入れてみよっか
It's a little thick so it's as far as I can go.
ちょっと太いからいけるところまで
That's great.
すごいいけるね
amazing.
すごい
It's a leg hole.
足の穴ですよ
Please take it in and out slowly.
ゆっくり出し入れしてね
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Please go home without washing.
洗わずに帰ってね
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました